var nombreDelJuego = "ARTICULO 1 CONSTITUCION ESPAÑOLA";

var absolutamentetodaslaspreguntas = [
    {
        "pregunta": "Estaba sucio",
        "respuesta": "Estado social",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "estado social",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "Demonio derecho",
        "respuesta": "Democratico de derecho",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "democratico derecho",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "Pulpo",
        "respuesta": "Pluralismo político",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "pluralismo politico",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "Juli",
        "respuesta": "Justicia y libertad",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "justicia libertad",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "Higos",
        "respuesta": "Igualdad",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "igualdad",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "Soberano",
        "respuesta": "Soberanía",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "soberania",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "Pueblo",
        "respuesta": "Pueblo",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "pueblo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "Vomita",
        "respuesta": "Emanan",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "emanan",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-,hermana-emanan",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "Powder",
        "respuesta": "Poderes",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "poderes",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "En Estado",
        "respuesta": "Estado",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "estado",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "En forma",
        "respuesta": "La forma",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "forma",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "Mona",
        "respuesta": "Monarquía",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "monarquia",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "Habla",
        "respuesta": "Parla",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "parla",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    }
];